Guide to the Catalogue Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records of Catalog Dept.; classification books, pamphlets, schemes, and lists of classified material, 1910-1995; Accession 1997-A-058
  - Classification K, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Reporting Yale's serial holdings to The Library of Congress, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Alphabetical table, Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Outline of Oxford and Cambridge University classification, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Subject subdivisions for individual universities and colleges, Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - L.C., class L, revisions, Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Classification scheme for shorthand, Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Principles of condensing classification schedules, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - State tables, Undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Country, state, and city tables, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Subdivisions used by New York City library, Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Classification memoranda, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Practical theory, Mv-Mx, Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Classification, Medicine, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - English languages, dialects, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Classification, class R, Medicine, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Classification, class G, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Classification, class H, Social Science, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Classification, class N, Fine Arts, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Classification, class Uz, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Classification, class R, Medicine, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Classification, class T, technology, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Classification, class H, Social Sciences, 1910 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Economic Theory, Public Finance, Statistics, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Records of Martha Conway as catalog management librarian [computer files], 1996-2001; Accession 2002-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - @Work, 1570 computer files (DOC, WPD, PDF, XLS, PPT, JPG, TXT)
    General note
    Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
  - Eudora email, 332
  - Recon serials catalog, 7 computer files (DOC, PDF)
- Yale University Library catalog [microfilm], circa 1975; Accession 2002-A-101 (Box 1–9)
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Retrospective conversion historical files, 1912-1999; Accession 2013-A-035
  Restricted until January 1, 2034.
  - Classification Class X, 1937-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Classification Class N, 1936-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Classification Class L, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Classification Class J, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Classification Class H, 1949-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Classification Class G, 1932-1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Classification Class E, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Classification Class C, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Classification Class B, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Classification Class A, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Classification Pamphlets Broad Classified, 1946-1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Catalogue, Expasion Official, 1945-1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Catalogue, Public, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cards Printed from Libraries other than LC, 1931-1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Card Reproduction, 1952-1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cards, Exchange of, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bingham Oceanographic Library, 1954-1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bibliography Room, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Babylonian Seminar, 1942-1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Atlas Collection Maps, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Art Library, 1932-1952 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Classics Library, 1945-1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chemistry Library, 1946-1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Catalogs Expansion, 1945-1954 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cataloguing: Non-Roman Alphabet Material, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cataloguing: Printed Cards vs. Original, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cataloguing: Descriptive, 1947-1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Filing Discussions, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Conrad Collection, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Chataqua Collection, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Baskerville Collection (Betts - ending of), 1935-1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Asch Collection, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Pequot Collection, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Penniman Collection, 1926-1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Collections: Mountaineering, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Madan Collection, 1932-1936 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Judaica, 1938-1957 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Collections: Franklin, 1936-1946 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - College Libraries - Timothy Dwight, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cole Collection, 1937-1945 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bibliography of Coe Bird Books, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Collections: Coe Bird Books, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Atlas Collection, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Collections: Andrews Study, 1945-1951 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Collections: American Musical Theatre, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Catalog Expansion Public, 1945-1953 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Collections - Wagner, 1923-1928 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Vaganay Collection, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Time-life Book Collection, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Tacitus Collection, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Collections: Stevenson, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Collections: Speck, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Collections: Shaw, 1934-1945 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Salisbury Collection, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Collections - Sala, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Russell Collection, 1933-1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Ruskin Collection, 1929-1934 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Riant Collection, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Reed Carol Collection, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Collections - Menus, 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Marcus Aurelius, 1931-1934 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Linton Collection, 1942-1952 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Collections: Karpinski, 1945-1953 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - J. W. Johnson Collection, 1949-1974 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Kanzer Collection, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Juvenal (Marston gift), 1936 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Collections: J. W. Johnson, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Incunabula, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - House Collection, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Hopson Collection, 1937-1944 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Collections - Hillhouse, 1931-1935 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Heine Collection, 1930-1946 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Garvan, Sheldon Collection, 1938-1944 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Gibson Collection, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Garvan, Ireland Collection, 1934-1948 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Fielding Collection, 1922-1947 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Dickens Collection, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Collections, Dexter, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Depew Collection, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Defoe Collection, 1937-1945 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - YCAL Collection, 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Collections: Yale Memorabilia, 1924-1953 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Copies, Added, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Connecticut Imprints, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Connecticut Hall, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Computer Center, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - College Libraries, 1933-1955 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - College Libraries - Timothy Dwight, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - College Libraries - Morse and Stiles, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Collections - Youth Movement, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Filing, 1942-1965 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Filing Rules - Departmental Libraries, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Farmington Plan, 1948-1962 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Engineering Library, 1924-1954 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Elizabethan Club, 1912-1924 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Econ. Growth Center, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Drama Library, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Documents Division, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Documents, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Divinity Library, 1940-1954 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Cowles Foundation, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Collections: Yale Memorabilia 1742, 1952-1982 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Collections: Wright (Howell), 1941-1955 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Collections: 1742 Yale Library Books, 1933-1945 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Collections: Western Americana, 1948-1957 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Dissertations, 1934-1958 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Departmental Library Cards, 1937-1956 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Departmental Libraries General Memo, 1919-1961 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Retrospective Conversion, Circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Profiles - OCLC, Circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - MICF, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Reclass, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Recon Services Agreement, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Art / Architecture Recon, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Medical Recon, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Recon Monographs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Recon Medical Library, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Divinity, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Art Recon, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Misc. Recon Procedures, Circa 1996 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Art, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Memorandum / Matching Guidelines, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Recon References, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Recon Corporate Bodies, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Recon Geographic Names, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Medical Library Recon Operators Instructions, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Filing, 1928-1948 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Filing, Sorting Cards for, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Retrospective Conversion (Yale), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - OCLC/ORBIS Conversion Specification, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Classification Class P, Circa 1945 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Classification Class Y, Circa 1945 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Classification Class Zn Numismatic, Circa 1945 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Training Presentation Examples and Documents Marc Fr.Edit, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Disbursement: 155 Whitney Avenue, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Classification, General, 1927-1958 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - L and B, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - L and B, 1930-1955 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Classification - Geology, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Classification - Chemistry Lab, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Yale Classification Principle, Pre-Conference Summaries, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Classification: LC Decisions, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Classification: LC, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Cataloging Descriptive, 1949-1967 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Meetings of April 23 and 30th, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Geology Library, 1940-1962 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Historical Sounds Recordings, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - German Reading Room, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Headings - Official, 1939-1946 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - History Seminar Library, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Forestry Library, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Folio Call Numbers, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Franklin Classification, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Geography Library, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Retrospective Conversion RFP Evaluation Committee Report, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Records, 1924-2008; Accession 2015-A-053
  Restricted until January 1, 2043
  - Official Catalog Boxes, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Official Catalog Recon: No call number, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Catalog Maintenance Backlog Reduction Project, 1989-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Catalog Management Recon Reports, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Catalog Management, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - College Libraries, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Collection Collaboratives, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Catalog Department Workflows and Requirements, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Card Catalogs, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Card Cataloging Vagaries, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Orbis Cataloging Procedures, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Vision (Cataloging Department), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cataloging Coordinating Committee (CCC), 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Filing Rules, 1959-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Collection Space Management, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Core Level Cataloging Experiment, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cataloging Local Headings, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Finding aid platform, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bibco-Yale, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Finding Aid Program, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Finding Aid Steering Committee, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Babylonian Project, 1998-2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Action Planning, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Davis Grant: documents and meeting minutes, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 23A)
  - DRS: Duke/Dartmouth Project, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - DRS: Reports & Presentations, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - BEINECKE: Purchase Agreements for Photo Archives, 1995-2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arabic and Middle Eastern Electronic Library (AMEEL), 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Finding Aid Authoring Tool, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cataloging Department Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Geographic Information System, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Digital Production and Integration Program (DPIP): Final Report, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Digital Production and Integration Program (DPIP): Contributions, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Digital Production and Integration Program (DPIP), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Grant Proposals: Cuba Collection, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Collections Collaborative: Steering Committee Meeting, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Collections Collaborative SC 3/29/07, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Collections Collaborative Symposium 5/17/07, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Collections Collaborative Miscellaneous, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Collections Collaborative Meeting 2/2/07, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Collections Collaborative Meeting 11/30/06, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Collections Collaborative Catering, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - CT History Online Project: Documents, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Casalini Records, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Collection Space Management: Steering Committee (LSF/SML), 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Collection Space Mangement: Swing Space, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cataloging of Serials, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Proposal to Establish a "Frontlog", 1996 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Collection Space Management (MUDD), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Collection Space Mangement (General), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Collection Space Management (CCL), 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - LC Reclassification, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Uncategorized Publications in Stacks, 1933-1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dust Jackets, 1938-1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dotting the Titles, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Collections - General, 1937-1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Collation, 1932-1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Faculty and Library Schools, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Classification - Langhorne Gibson, 1934-1957 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Classification - Technology, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Classification - Statistics, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Classification - Selections from Newspaper and Periods, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Classification - Science, 1941-1953 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Classification - Red Cross, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Classification - Notation, 1937-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Classification - Radio, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Classification - Monograph Series, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Classification - Judaica and Latin America, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Classification - Intelligence, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Classification - Illustrated Books, 1931-1938 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Classification - Hymnology, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Classification - Atomic Energy, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Classification - Arms and Armor, 1930-1955 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Classification - Antiquities, Archaeology, Civilization and Culture, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Classification - Anthropo-geography, 1928-1945 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Classification - Almanacs, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Catholic University - Cataloging of Catholics Imprints, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cataloging Statistics - DCC, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cataloging - Simplified (Brief), 1944-1959 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cataloging - Costs, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cataloging in Source, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Catalogue Department - Space Needs (25 years), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Catalogue Department Memos, 1959-1964 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Catalogue Department Memos, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Catalogue Department Flow of Work, 1960-1972 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Catalogue Department (General), 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cancel - Cancelled, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Statistics, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Catalogue Department - American Tracts File, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Yale University Library - Atlas Collection and Map Room, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Astronomy Library, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Weekly Statistics [Old Acq], 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Reference Collection, 1971-1980 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Union Shelf List, 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Official Catalog, 1928-1955 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Series and Serials, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Zeta, 1965-1974 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Lewis Walpole Library, 1977-1986 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Tibetan Collection, 1958-1983 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Southeast Asian Collection, 1966-1979 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Social Science Library, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Romanization, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Latin American Collection, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - LC Classification at Yale, 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Mathematics Library, 1958-1971 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Kline Science Library, 1965-1981 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Judaic Studies Reference, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Near Eastern Collection, 1970-1989 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Epidemiology, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Divinity Library, 1973-1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Catalogues, Card, 1954-1985 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Shelving, 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Shelf List and Shelf Cards, 1934-1962 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Reclassification Project, 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Numismastics Collection, 1962-1972 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Bibliography Room, 1969-1979 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - British Art, 1970-1981 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Catalogue, Public - Measurement and scope, 1955-1988 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Catalog - Expansion - Public, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Classical authors - Organized headings, 1952-1984 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - College libraries, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Cross Campus Library, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Departmental Libraries, 1962-1980 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - East Asian Collection, 1968-1981 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Disserations, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - American Oriental Society, 1922-1989 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Government Publications, 1969-1981 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Art Library, 1969-1986 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Atlas Collection, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Transliteration, 1934-1959 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Semitic Reference Library, 1938-1959 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Special Files, 1945-1960 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Sociology Library, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Serials, 1939-1957 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Serial Statement Cards, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Reserve Book Room, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Reprints - Call Number, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Reclassing, 1945-1950 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Political Science Library, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Physics Library, 1946-1967 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Peabody Museum, 1950-1964 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Parliamentary Papers, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Pamphets - Pre-1800s, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Pamphets, 1947-1971 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - American Oriental Society, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Philosiphical Library, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Art Library, 1938-1953 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Yale Memorabibia, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Walpole Library, 1949-1962 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Voluminous Authors: Shortened Form of Name, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Ornithology Library, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Observatory Library, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Non-Romanized Alphabet Languages - Yale Holdings, 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Music Library, 1924-1953 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - More House Library, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Microtext Room, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Microfilms - Miscellaneous, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Microfilms - MSS, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Medical Theses, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Medical Library, 1947-1967 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Mathematical Seminary, 1926-1960 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Maps and Map Room, 1938-1948 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Linguistic Seminar, 1954-1965 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Latin American Pamphets, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Latin American Collection, 1926-1959 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Judaica Collection, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - International Relations, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Shorthand Collection, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Connecticut Newspapers, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Connecticut Newspaper Project, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Annual Report Catalogue Department 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Annual Report Catalogue Department 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Annual Report Catalogue Department 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Annual Report Catalogue Department 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report Catalogue Department 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report Catalogue Department 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Voyager 2000.1 Cataloging Manual (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Subject Manual, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Filing Lessons, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Staff Manual, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cataloging of Serials (Third Edition), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Future catalog, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Sample Card Manual, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9A)
  - Serials Division Adding Manual, 1958-1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Serials Notes, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Getting Ready for AACR2, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Medical Records, 1930-1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Voyager 2000.1 Acquisition Manual (Box 3, Folder 14-16)
  - Cataloging and Acquisition Departmental Manual, New Edition / introduction Edward A. Jaiko and Mildred E. Dugas (Head Librarian), 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Task Force/Core Level Cataloging, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Table of Contents Enrichment, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Task Force on Delsey Report, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Team Leaders, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Task Force on Preservation Reproductions Cataloging, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Strategic Planning - Library, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Strategic Plan and Values, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Strategic Planning - Library, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bibliograph Control Goal Group, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Pinyin Conversion (Chinese - from Wade-Giles), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Research Library Information Network, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Technical Service Management Group, 1996-2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Improving Services in CCL & the Entry Floors of SML: Review and Planning Retreat, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Technical Service Management Group, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Technical Service Steering Cart, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Library Management Council: Fiscal Year 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Library Management Council: Fiscal Year 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Library Management Council: Fiscal Year 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Library Management Council: Fiscal Year 2006, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Library Management Council: Budget Committee, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Library Management Council: Fiscal Year 2006, 2004-2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Art Metadata, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Art Metadata, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)